JENEIA D. MULLINS

NEW YORK, NY

PHONE: 336-263-3881 | EMAIL: Jeneia.Mullins@gmail.com

LINKEDIN: www.linkedin.com/in/jeneia | GITHUB: https://github.com/JD-FinTech

SUMMARY

Leveraged finance and capital markets professional with recent experience in digital innovation, design thinking, and machine learning development. Currently enrolled in an intensive FinTech Bootcamp at Columbia University Engineering to develop deep learning, natural language processing, and blockchain analytical models.

Trusted within the financial services industry for expertise, honesty, loyalty, commitment, and for upholding a strong controls environment. Experience building and leading teams while developing the next generation of leadership talent.

RELEVANT SKILLS

FINANCIAL TECH

- Leveraged Finance: Underwriting due diligence, legal document negotiation, LBO modeling, capital markets syndication, lender presentations, portfolio monitoring
- Coverage (Corporate & Sponsor): Building relationships with C-Suite from founders and executives to Sponsors offering commercial and investment banking products // Licenses: Series 7, 63, 79
- Programming: Python, JSON, MySQL, Tensorflow, SiKitLearn, Amazon Web Services, Crypto Currency, Eurytherm Blockchain
- AI & ML: Natural language processing and sentiment analysis of quarterly earnings reports, building deep neural networks to forecast financial models and predict future stock prices

WORK EXPERIENCE

JP MORGAN CHASE 2013 - PRESENT

Middle Market Banking Digital Transformation – Executive Director

2018 - Present

- Responsibilities: Developing new financial products across commercial and investment banking utilizing design thinking, machine learning, and product development to drive innovation across JPMC
- Prioritize and manage a portfolio of use cases as liaison between business leaders and technology execution
- Highlights: Created end-to-end client experience design of product recommendation and solutioning engine

Financial Sponsors Group Originations & Execution – Executive Director

2016 - 201

- Responsibilities: Originations and deal execution of capital markets and commercial banking transactions
- Highlights: Led due diligence and structuring of >75 transactions ranging from \$25 to \$1BN in deal size
- Awards: Received 2017 Women's Bond Club Rising Star Award external industry recognition

Corporate Banking Coverage – Vice President

2013 - 2016

- Responsibilities: Developed top tier client relationships with C-Suite of middle market companies
- Highlights: Launched successful IPO for Shake Shack and won agent lead position on KIND Snacks

GE CAPITAL

2005 – 2013

Antares Sponsor Finance – Credit Structing and Underwriting Associate

- Responsibilities: Conducted due diligence, transaction structuring, legal document negotiation, deal closing, lender syndication, and portfolio management across senior secured, second lien, and equity tag positions
- Highlights: Underwrote \$4.7BN in senior secured commitments with average deal size of \$400MM

Bank Loan Group – Market Research and Trading Associate

2007 - 2010

- Responsibilities: Analyzed \$4BN in credit trades, gained exposure to dressed workouts during recession
- Highlights: Developed risk metrics reporting package on \$1.5BN portfolio of distressed investments

GE Financial Management Program

2005 - 2007

• Responsibilities: Rotations included Financial Planning & Analysis, Product Line Profitability, Working Capital Financial Analysis, and Commercial Sales and Industry Analysis

EDUCATION

COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY – SCHOOL OF ENGINEERING

FINTECH PROGRAM CERTIFICATE

2019 - 2020

<u>Description</u>: Intensive FinTech hands-on course coding in python and JSON to solve problems using machine learning, natural language processing, predictive financial forecasting, blockchain solutions on an Amazon Web Services cloud

ELON UNIVERSITY – INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS AND FINANCE BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

2001 - 2005

<u>Description</u>: Graduated Summa Cum Laude with a Bachelor of Science in International Business and a minor in Spanish, studied abroad in Toledo, Spain and interned in London at Thomson Financial in 2004 (*GPA*: 3.9/4.0)